

Jatin Khatter

Full Stack Developer

An ardent web developer, lifelong learner, and expert in front-end web development, ReactJS, NodeJS, MongoDB, and web networking knowledge are required. high adaptability to learning new technologies quickly and paying attention to details. It aims to leverage knowledge and build world-class Web applications while facilitating the organisation in achieving functional goals.

iatinkhatter789@gmail.com

Faridabad (Delhi NCR), India

github.com/JatinKhatter07

+91-9582455721

in linkedin.com/in/jatin-khatter-7b7166217

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Full Stack Web Development. (Full time) Masai School

04/2022 - Present

Bengaluru, Karnataka.

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech) Maharishi Dayanand University Haryana

08/2016 - 08/2020 Faridabad, Haryana.

Intermediate.

Central Board of Secondary Education.

04/2014 - 05/2016

Faridabad, Haryana

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Development Associate. BYJU's The Learing App.

10/2021 - 05/2022 Noida, UP BYJUS's is an Indian multinational educational technology company.

Senior Civil Engineer. HRH City Projects Pvt. Ltd.

11/2020 - 08/2021 Faridabad, Haryana Construction company (Developing Affordable residential High rise towers.)

SOFT SKILLS

Collaboration

Problem-Solving.

Remote-Work

Communication.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

ReactJS, NodeJS.

Visual Studio Code, GitHub.

PROJECTS

AirGarage-Clone (Website)

- o AirGarage is a full-service parking operator. It handles all of the day-to-day logistics that go into making your parking lot or garage the most successful version of itself.
- Features: Social Sign-in | Sign-up | Single Page Application.
- o Tech Stack: ReactJS | JSON-Server | Chakra-UI.
- o Area of responsibility: Created Navbar | Footer | GitHub Handling.
- Deployment Link :
- GitHub :

Fitness Blender-Clone (Website)

- o Fitness Blender is an American digital fitness content publisher founded by personal trainers Kelli and Daniel Segars.
- Collaborative Project: Accomplished with of 4 developers.
- o Features: Social Sign-in | Sign-up | Cart | Import Export.
- Teck Stack: HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Local-storage | JSON-Server
- Area of responsibility: Created Product Page | Cart Page | Authentication feature | GitHub Handling.
- Deployment Link :
- GitHub Link :

INTERESTS

Reading Books

Bike Riding

Trading

Trekking.